<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<!--  Use this to test local rendering in firefox -->
<!-- ?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="project-plan-render.xsl"? --> 

<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="http://www.eclipse.org/projects/project-plan.xsl"?>
<p:plan plan-format="1.0" xmlns:p="http://www.eclipse.org/project/plan" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml"
      name="Equinox">
   <p:release projectid="rt.equinox" version="Galileo"/>
    <p:introduction><div>
<hr/>
<div style="align:center;"><big><b>Preliminary</b></big></div>

<p>
Equinox is way cool.

</p>
Table of contents:
<ul>
  <li><a href="#m_release_deliverables">Release Deliverables</a></li>
  <li><a href="#m_release_milestones">Release Milestones</a></li>
  <li><a href="#m_target_environments">Target Environments</a></li>
  <li><a href="#m_compatibility">Compatibility</a></li>
  <li><a href="#m_themes">Themes and Priorities</a>
	  <ul>
	  	<li><a href="#tp_tcf">Tentative: OSGi Spec implementation</a></li>
	   	<li><a href="#tp_other">Other</a></li>
	  </ul>
  </li>
</ul>
  </div></p:introduction>
  <p:release_deliverables><div>
<ul>
	<li><b><a name="m_release_deliverables">Equinox</a> source code release</b>, available as versions tagged "R3_5" in the project's
		<ul>
			<li><a href="http://dev.eclipse.org/viewcvs/index.cgi/org.eclipse.tm.rse/?cvsroot=DSDP_Project">RSE CVS Repository</a>,</li>
			<li><a href="http://dev.eclipse.org/viewcvs/index.cgi/org.eclipse.tm.core/?cvsroot=DSDP_Project">TM Core CVS Repository</a>, and</li>
			<li><a href="http://dev.eclipse.org/viewcvs/index.cgi/org.eclipse.tm.tcf/trunk/?root=DSDP_SVN">TM TCF SVN Repository</a>.</li>
		</ul>
	</li>
	<li><b>Framework:</b>
		<ul>
		   <li>bunch o stuff here.</li>
    	</ul>
    </li>
	<li><b>Framework:</b>
		<ul>
		   <li>bunch o stuff here.</li>
    	</ul>
    </li>
</ul>
<b>Notes:</b>
<p> stuff here </p>

  </div></p:release_deliverables>
  <p:release_milestones>
    <p:preamble><p>      
<a name="m_release_milestones">Release milestones</a>
will be occurring at roughly 6 week intervals, and will be aligned with the
<a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/Galileo_Simultaneous_Release">
Galileo Simultaneous Release</a> train.
    </p></p:preamble>
    <p:milestone date="10/1/2008" milestone="M2"><div>3.5M2</div></p:milestone>
    <p:milestone date="11/12/2008" milestone="M3"><div>3.5M3</div></p:milestone>
    <p:milestone date="12/29/2008" milestone="M4"><div>3.5M4</div></p:milestone>
    <p:milestone date="2/6/2009" milestone="M5"><div>3.5M5</div></p:milestone>
    <p:milestone date="3/18/2009" milestone="M6"><div>3.5M6 (API Freeze)</div></p:milestone>
    <p:milestone date="5/5/2009" milestone="M7"><div>3.5M7 (Feature Freeze)</div></p:milestone>
    <p:milestone date="5/19/2009" milestone="RC1"><div>3.5RC1</div></p:milestone>
    <p:milestone date="5/26/2009" milestone="RC2"><div>3.5RC2</div></p:milestone>
    <p:milestone date="6/2/2009" milestone="RC3"><div>3.5RC3</div></p:milestone>
    <p:milestone date="6/9/2009" milestone="RC4"><div>3.5RC4</div></p:milestone>
    <p:postamble><div>
A detailed <a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/DSDP/TM/3.1_Ramp_down_Plan">
TM 3.1 Ramp down Plan</a> towards the release is available especially for the Eclipse 
<a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/Galileo_Simultaneous_Release">
Galileo Simultaneous Release</a> integration.
<p>
The target date for availability of Equinox 3.5 is:</p>
<ul>
	<li>Wednesday June 24, 2009 - Equinox 3.5 Release date (with Galileo)</li>
</ul>
    </div></p:postamble>
  </p:release_milestones>

  <p:target_environments><div>
<a name="m_target_environments">In order</a>
<p>In order to remain current, each Equinox release targets reasonably current
  operating environments. </p>
<p>Most of Equinox is &quot;pure&quot; Java code and has no direct dependence
  on the underlying operating system. The chief dependence is therefore on the
  Java Platform itself. Portions of Equinox are targeted to specific classes of operating
  environments, requiring their source code to only reference facilities available
  in particular class libraries (e.g. J2ME Foundation 1.0, J2SE 1.3 and 1.4,
  etc.). </p>
<p> In general, the 3.5 release of Equinox is developed for a mix
  of J2ME Foundation 1.0 and 1.1 JREs. Certain bundles do however use facilities in more
  recent JRE versions.  In such cases, the associated capabilities are available when
  running on the required JRE. </p>
<p> <a href="#Appendix1">Appendix 1</a> contains a table that indicates the class
  library level required for each bundle. </p>

<p>There are many different implementations of the Java Platform running atop
  a variety of operating systems. We focus Equinox testing on a handful of
  popular combinations of operating system and Java Platform; these are our <em>reference
  platforms</em>. Equinox undoubtedly runs fine in many operating environments
  beyond the reference platforms we test, including those using Java6 VMs. However,
  since we do not systematically test them we cannot vouch for them. Problems
  encountered when running Equinox on a non-reference platform that cannot be
  recreated on any reference platform will be given lower priority than problems
  with running Equinox on a reference platform.</p>
<p> Equinox 3.5 is tested and validated on the following reference platforms
(<img src="new.gif" alt="(new)" border="0" height="12" width="12" /> multiple updates)
  (this list is updated over the course of the release cycle):</p>
<center>
  <table border="1" cellpadding="2" cellspacing="2" width="80%" summary="Equinox Reference Platforms">
    <tbody>
      <tr align="center">
        <td><b>Reference Platforms</b></td>

      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>Microsoft Windows Vista, x86-32, Win32</b> running (any of):
          <ul>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14 for Microsoft Windows</li>
            <li>IBM 32-bit SDK for Windows, Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR6b</li>
            <li>BEA JRockit 27.4.0, for Microsoft Windows</li>

          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>Microsoft Windows XP, x86-32, Win32</b> running (any of):
          <ul>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 6.0 Update 4 for Microsoft Windows</li>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14 for Microsoft Windows</li>

            <li>IBM 32-bit SDK for Windows, Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR6b</li>
            <li>BEA JRockit 27.4.0, for Microsoft Windows</li>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 1.4.2_16 for Microsoft Windows</li>
            <li>IBM 32-bit SDK for Windows, Java 2 Technology Edition 1.4.2 SR10</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>

        <td><b>Red Hat Enterprise Linux 5.0, x86-32, GTK</b> running (any of):
          <ul>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14 for Linux x86</li>
            <li>IBM 32-bit SDK for Linux on Intel architecture, Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR6b</li>
            <li>BEA JRockit 27.4.0, for Linux x86</li>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 1.4.2_16 for Linux x86</li>

            <li>IBM 32-bit SDK for Linux on Intel architecture, Java 2 Technology Edition 1.4.2 SR10</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 10, x86-32, GTK</b> running (any
          of):
          <ul>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14 for Linux x86</li>

            <li>IBM 32-bit SDK for Linux on Intel architecture, Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR6b</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>Microsoft Windows Vista, x86-64, Win32</b> running (any of):
          <ul>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14 for Microsoft Windows (AMD64/EM64T)</li>

            <li>IBM 64-bit SDK for Windows, Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR6b</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>Microsoft Windows XP Professional x64 Edition, x86-64, Win32</b> running (any of):
          <ul>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14 for Microsoft Windows (AMD64/EM64T)</li>

            <li>IBM 64-bit SDK for Windows, Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR6b</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>Red Hat Enterprise Linux 4.0 update 2, x86-64, GTK</b> running:
          <ul>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14 for Linux x86_64</li>

          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>Sun Solaris 10, SPARC, GTK</b> running:
          <ul>
            <li>Sun Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 14 for Solaris SPARC</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>

      <tr>
        <td><b>HP-UX 11i v2, ia64, Motif 2.1, GTK</b> running:
          <ul>
            <li>HP-UX Java 2 Standard Edition 5.0 Update 7 for Itanium</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>IBM AIX 5.3, Power, Motif 2.1</b> running:
          <ul>

            <li>IBM 32-bit SDK, Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR6b</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>Red Hat Enterprise Linux 5.0, Power, GTK</b> running:
          <ul>
            <li>IBM 32-bit SDK for Linux on pSeries architecture, Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR6b</li>

          </ul></td>
      </tr>
      <tr>
        <td><b>SUSE Linux Enterprise Server 10, Power, GTK</b> running:
          <ul>
            <li>IBM 32-bit SDK for Linux on pSeries architecture, Java 2 Technology Edition 5.0, SR6b</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>

      <tr>
        <td><b>Apple Mac OS X 10.5, Universal, Carbon</b> running:
          <ul>
            <li>Apple Java 2 Platform Standard Edition (J2SE) 5, service release 4</li>
          </ul></td>
      </tr>
    </tbody>
  </table>

</center>
<p>Because Java 1.4.2 and Java5 based platforms are used for most Eclipse development,
  those platforms are listed here. Although there are teams doing some Java 6
  based development we have not included specific Java6 VMs, since they have
  not yet received the general level of testing we require. <i>We expect that
  Equinox works fine on other current Java VMs and OSes but we cannot flag these as reference 
  platforms without significant community support for testing them. Especially in areas such as 
  the launcher and OS security integration.</i></p>
 <p>As Equinox is largely headless, there are very few dependencies on window systems.
 Where there are UI elements (e.g., in the p2 UI), these elements will work on any configuration 
 supported by SWT.</p>

  </div><p:internationalization>
<p>Equinox is designed as the basis for internationalized products. The
  user interface elements provided by Equinox components, including dialogs
  and error messages, are externalized. The English strings are provided as the
  default resource bundles.</p>
<p>Latin-1 and DBCS locales are supported by Equinox on all reference platforms;
  BIDI locales are supported by Equinox everywhere but on Motif.</p>
<p>Equinox supports GB 18030 (level 1), the Chinese code page standard,
  on Windows XP and 2000, Linux/GTK and the Macintosh.</p>
<p>German and Japanese locales are tested.</p>
    </p:internationalization>
  </p:target_environments>
 
  <p:compatibility_with_previous_releases><div>
<p><a name="m_compatibility">Equinox 3.5</a> will be backward compatible with Equinox 3.4 (and, hence, with 3.3, 3.2, 3.1
  and 3.0).</p>
<p> <strong>API Contract Compatibility:</strong> Equinox 3.5 will be upwards
  contract-compatible with Equinox 3.4 except in those areas noted in the <a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/Equinox_Galileo_Porting_Guide" target="_top"> <em>Equinox
  3.5 Migration Guide</em></a>. Programs that use affected APIs and extension
  points will need to be ported to Equinox 3.5 APIs. Downward contract compatibility
  is not supported. There is no guarantee that compliance with Equinox 3.5
  APIs would ensure compliance with Equinox 3.4 APIs. Refer to <a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/index.php/Evolving_Java-based_APIs"> <em>Evolving
  Java-based APIs</em> </a> for a discussion of the kinds of API changes that
  maintain contract compatibility. </p>
<p><strong>Binary (bundle) Compatibility:</strong> Equinox 3.5 will be upwards
  binary-compatible with Equinox 3.4 except in those areas noted in the <a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/Equinox_Galileo_Porting_Guide" target="_top"> <em>Equinox
  3.5 Migration Guide</em></a>. Downward bundle compatibility is not
  supported. Bundles for Equinox 3.5 will not in general be usable in Equinox 3.4.
  Refer to <a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/index.php/Evolving_Java-based_APIs"> <em>Evolving
  Java-based APIs</em> </a> for a discussion of the kinds of API changes that
  maintain binary compatibility. </p>
<p><strong>Source Compatibility:</strong> Equinox 3.5 will be upwards source-compatible
  with Equinox 3.4 except in the areas noted in the <a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/Equinox_Galileo_Porting_Guide" target="_top"> <em>Equinox
  3.5 Migration Guide</em></a>. This means that source files written
  to use Equinox 3.4 APIs might successfully compile and run against Equinox
  3.5 APIs, although this is not guaranteed. Downward source compatibility
  is not supported. If source files use new Equinox APIs, they will not be
  usable with an earlier version of Equinox. </p>
<p><strong>Non-compliant usage of API's</strong>: All non-API methods and classes,
  and certainly everything in a package with &quot;internal&quot; in its name or those
  packages marked with &quot;x-internal=true&quot; or with &quot;x-friends&quot; annotations,
  are considered implementation details which may vary between operating environment
  and are subject to change without notice. Client bundles that directly depend
  on anything other than what is specified in the Equinox API are inherently
  unsupportable and receive no guarantees about compatibility within a single
  release much less with earlier releases. Refer to <a href="http://www.eclipse.org/articles/Article-API%20use/eclipse-api-usage-rules.html"> <em>How
  to Use the Eclipse API</em> </a> for information about how to write compliant
  bundles. </p>
</div></p:compatibility_with_previous_releases>
  
  
  <p:themes_and_priorities>
    <p:preamble><div>
<p>Plan items listed <a name="m_themes">below</a> were defined according to
 contributor requirements and the Eclipse <a href="http://wiki.eclipse.org/RequirementsCouncilThemesAndPriorities">
Themes and Priorities</a>
set forth by the Eclipse Requirements Council.
Each plan item covers a feature or API that is to be added to the 
Equinox deliverables, or some aspect of the Equinox Project that is to be improved. Each plan item has its 
own entry in the Eclipse bugzilla database, with a title and a 
concise summary (usually a single paragraph) that explains the 
work item at a suitably high enough level so that everyone can 
readily understand what the work item is without having to understand
the nitty-gritty detail. 
</p>
<p>Not all plan items represent the same amount of work; some may be quite
large, others, quite small. Although some plan items are for work that is 
more pressing than others, the plan items appear in no particular order.
See the corresponding bugzilla items for up-to-date status information on
ongoing work and planned delivery milestones.
</p>
<p>The current status of each plan item is noted:
</p>
<ul>
  <li><b>Committed</b> plan item - A committed plan item is one that we have
    decided to address for the release. In bugzilla, this is reflected by
    having a concrete target milestone assigned.</li>
  <li><b>Proposed</b> plan item - A proposed plan item is one that we are
    considering addressing for the release. Although we are actively
    investigating it, we are not yet in a position to commit to it, or to say
    that we won't be able to address it. After due consideration, a proposal
    will either be committed or deferred. In bugzilla, such items are reflected
    by having a target milestone "3.5" or "---" assigned.</li>
  <li><b>Deferred</b> plan item - A reasonable proposal that will not make it in
    to this release for some reason is marked as deferred with a brief note as
    to why it was deferred. Deferred plan items may resurface as committed plan
    items at a later point. In bugzilla, such items are reflected by having
    a target milestone "Future" assigned.</li>
</ul>
    </div></p:preamble>

<!-- +++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++ -->
<!-- Query: Committed = target_milestone LIKE %3.1+M[234567]% AND NOT priority=P5  -->
<!-- Query: Proposed  = target_milestone IN [ 3.1 , - ]       AND NOT priority=P5  AND resolution=-  -->
<!-- Query: Deferred  = target_milestone IS Future            AND NOT priority=P5  AND resolution=-  -->
<!-- +++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++++ -->

    <p:theme name="Tentative: OSGi spec implementation">
      <p:description><p>
The <a name="tp_spec">OSGi Alliance</a>, in collaboration with Equinox and other open source communities, is currently 
revising the Core specifications. As the reference implementation for several parts of the OSGi specifications, 
Equinox will be updated to implement these new features and changes to the spec.
In bugzilla, these items are tagged with <b>"[spec]"</b> in the Summary
(query: <a href="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&amp;short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;short_desc=[spec%5D&amp;classification=RT&amp;product=Equinox&amp;component=Framework&amp;component=RSE&amp;component=Compendium&amp;component=Components&amp;bug_status=UNCONFIRMED&amp;bug_status=NEW&amp;bug_status=ASSIGNED&amp;bug_status=REOPENED&amp;cmdtype=doit">
all [spec] open</a>).
      </p></p:description>
      <!--  Query: short_desc LIKE %[spec]% -->
      <p:committed bugzilla="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&amp;short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;short_desc=[spec%5D&amp;classification=RT&amp;product=Equinox&amp;component=Framework&amp;component=RSE&amp;component=Compendium&amp;component=Components&amp;target_milestone=3.5+M2&amp;target_milestone=3.5+M3&amp;target_milestone=3.5+M4&amp;target_milestone=3.5+M5&amp;target_milestone=3.5+M6&amp;target_milestone=3.5+M7&amp;keywords_type=allwords&amp;keywords=&amp;priority=P1&amp;priority=P2&amp;priority=P3&amp;priority=P4&amp;cmdtype=doit"></p:committed>
      <p:proposed bugzilla="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&amp;short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;short_desc=[spec%5D&amp;classification=RT&amp;product=Equinox&amp;component=Framework&amp;component=RSE&amp;component=Compendium&amp;component=Components&amp;target_milestone=3.5&amp;target_milestone=---&amp;keywords_type=allwords&amp;keywords=&amp;resolution=---&amp;priority=P1&amp;priority=P2&amp;priority=P3&amp;priority=P4&amp;cmdtype=doit"></p:proposed>
      <p:deferred bugzilla="https://bugs.eclipse.org/bugs/buglist.cgi?query_format=advanced&amp;short_desc_type=allwordssubstr&amp;short_desc=[spec%5D&amp;classification=RT&amp;product=Equinox&amp;component=Framework&amp;component=RSE&amp;component=Compendium&amp;component=Components&amp;target_milestone=Future&amp;keywords_type=allwords&amp;keywords=&amp;resolution=---&amp;priority=P1&amp;priority=P2&amp;priority=P3&amp;priority=P4&amp;cmdtype=doit"></p:deferred>
    </p:theme>
    
    
  </p:themes_and_priorities>
  <p:appendix name="1">
  
  <h2><a name="Appendix1" id="Appendix1">Appendix 1: Execution Environment by Bundle</a></h2>
<p>In the table below, the &quot;3.5 minimum execution environment&quot;
  column indicates the minimum Java class library requirements of each bundle
  for the 3.4 release, where the value is one of:</p>
<table border="0" width="90%">
  <tbody>
    <tr>

      <td align="center"><b>Entry</b></td>
      <td align="left"><b>Meaning</b></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><div align="center"><strong>M1.0</strong></div></td>
      <td>OSGi Minimum Execution Environment 1.0 - This is a subset of the J2ME
        Foundation class libraries defined by OSGi to be the base for framework
        implementations. See the OSGi specification for more details.</td>
    </tr>

    <tr>
      <td width="9%"><div align="center"><strong>M1.1</strong></div></td>
      <td width="91%">OSGi Minimum Execution Environment 1.1 - This is a subset
        of the J2ME Foundation class libraries defined by OSGi to be the base
        for framework implementations. See the OSGi specification for more details.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><div align="center"><strong>F1.0</strong></div></td>
      <td>J2ME Foundation 1.0 - indicates that the bundle can only be run on
        Foundation 1.0 or greater. Note that with the exception of some MicroEdition
        IO classes, Foundation 1.0 is a subset of J2SE 1.3.</td>

    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><div align="center"><strong>F1.1</strong></div></td>
      <td>J2ME Foundation 1.1 - indicates that the bundle can only be run on
        Foundation 1.1 or greater. Note that with the exception of some MicroEdition
        IO classes, Foundation 1.1 is a subset of J2SE 1.4.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><div align="center"><strong>1.2</strong></div></td>

      <td>J2SE 1.2 - indicates that the bundle can only be run on JSE 1.2 or
        greater.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><div align="center"><strong>1.3</strong></div></td>
      <td>J2SE 1.3 - indicates that the bundle can only be run on JSE 1.3 or
        greater.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>

      <td><div align="center"><strong>1.4</strong></div></td>
      <td>J2SE 1.4 - indicates that the bundle can only be run on JSE 1.4 or
        greater.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><div align="center"><strong>1.4/1.5</strong></div></td>
      <td>Indicates that the bundle can run on JSE 1.4 or greater, but provides
        enhanced functionality when run on J2SE 5.0.</td>
    </tr>

    <tr>
      <td><div align="center"><strong>1.5</strong></div></td>
      <td>J2SE 5.0 - indicates that the bundle can only be run on JSE 5.0 or
        greater.</td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td><div align="center"><strong>1.6</strong></div></td>
      <td>J2SE 6.0 - indicates that the bundle can only be run on JSE 6.0 or
        greater.</td>

    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td align="center"><b>n/a</b></td>
      <td>Unknown at the time of this revision.</td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
<br />
<b>Table of minimum execution environments by bundle.</b> 
   (<img src="new.gif" alt="(new)" border="0" height="12" width="12" /> multiple updates)<br />

<br />

<table border="1">
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td width="290"><strong>Bundle</strong></td>
      <td width="60"><div align="center"><p align="center"><b>3.4<br/>minimum<br/>execution<br/>environment</b></p></div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>javax.servlet.jsp</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>javax.servlet</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.apache.commons.el</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.apache.commons.logging</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.apache.jasper</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.ecf.filetransfer</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.ecf.identity</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.ecf.provider.filetransfer.ssl</td>
      <td><div align="center">1.4</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.ecf.provider.filetransfer</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.ecf.ssl</td>
      <td><div align="center">1.4</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.ecf</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.app</td>
      <td><div align="center">M1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.common</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.frameworkadmin.equinox</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.frameworkadmin</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.http.jetty</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.http.registry</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.http.servlet</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.jsp.jasper.registry</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.jsp.jasper</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.launcher</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.artifact.repository</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.console</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.core</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.director.app</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.directorywatcher</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.director</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.engine</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.exemplarysetup</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.extensionlocation</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.garbagecollector</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.jarprocessor</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.metadata.generator</td>
      <td><div align="center">1.4</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.metadata.repository</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.metadata</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.reconciler.dropins</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.touchpoint.eclipse</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.touchpoint.natives</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.ui.sdk</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.ui</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.updatechecker</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.p2.updatesite</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.preferences</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.registry</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.security.ui</td>
      <td><div align="center">1.4</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.security</td>
      <td><div align="center">1.4</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.simpleconfigurator.manipulator</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.equinox.simpleconfigurator</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.osgi.services</td>
      <td><div align="center">M1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.osgi.util</td>
      <td><div align="center">M1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.eclipse.osgi</td>
      <td><div align="center">M1.1</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.mortbay.jetty</td>
      <td><div align="center">F1.0</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.sat4j.core</td>
      <td><div align="center">1.4</div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td>org.sat4j.pb</td>
      <td><div align="center">1.4</div></td>
    </tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
  </p:appendix>  
</p:plan>

